<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Doozy Infosystems</string>
    <string name="vision_heading">Vision</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Setting</string>
    <string name="skill_heading">Our Skill</string>
    <string name="skill_text">We have a skilled pool of professionals that have expertise in the latest mobile and web technologies, offering versatile information technology solutions.</string>
    <string name="vision_text">Our vision is to be a successful IT firm with high standards and gain respect for our work. We work towards being recognized globally and gain the trust and support of all our clients. We also believe to work towards a better future where we can provide more solutions for businesses to flourish.</string>
    <string name="mission_heading">Mission</string>
    <string name="mission_text">Our mission is to work towards our future vision. We provide high standard and qualitative solutions for our client’s business. Our solutions with no doubt is cost effective which means we value your money too and it shows that we work more for your satisfaction and to keep you with us by building a strong relation instead of just making short term gains. We maintain business ethics and values and do not cross the business boundaries. We deliver work on time without any compromises made on the quality. Our work is best in the industry and we give back much more to you which is beyond your expectations. We make sure we deliver what you need will make you come back to us for all your business projects in future.</string>
    <string name="values_heading">Our Values</string>
    <string name="values_text">We do not work for the sake of working. Our work is our passion. We work passionately to achieve your goals which are ultimately our goals too. We strongly believe in transparency and provide you with every little detail which you are ought to know. We are a reliable firm where you get full value for your money and time. You provide us with the work and the rest is our responsibility. You can rely on us for quality work. We are a premium employer who employs professionals after being sure that they are well qualified to work on your project and this is the reason that best of the professionals work here with us. We are innovative in nature and make innovations quite often as we realize that each company has its own requirements which have to be dealt with precision and different innovative approaches are to be used. We are the leading IT firm providing you and your business the best of software solutions which are high in quality and cost effective. Working with us assures professional assistance which is beneficial for your business ventures.</string>
    <string name="onWeb">On Web</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="shopping_cart">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity__about">Doozy Infosystems</string>
    <string name="title_activity_acting">ActingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">Item Details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cart">Cart Items</string>
    <string name="cartItemDetails">Item Details</string>
</resources>
